Yeah, I actually don't recommend doing
that at all. I recommend almost deleting
everything that the agent saves in its
own memory banks. In Claude code, you
can do this by going into memory and
just basically turning auto memory off
there. I just have it off completely.
When this is on, it saves it into a
local file called uppercase memory.md
and it uses this to remember your
preferences. Except it's just way too
freaking eager to remember your
preferences and save them some. And so
you will have some kind of preference
about a specific feature and how that
feature needs to be built and then that
will go into your memory banks and just
go everywhere and influence every single
conversation that you then have with the
agent. I much prefer my agent to be
completely stateless because when it's
stateless, you know, it doesn't remember
anything from previous sessions, then
it's much more predictable. I know how
it's going to behave because I work from
a consistent base every time. Whereas if
you have this memory build-up, this kind
of like
of all this kludge building up over
time, then every time you use it, it's
going to be slightly different, slightly
less predictable. You should be in
control of the steering. You should be
in control of choosing where you go and
that means if you have something at a
preference that you want to be
expressed, then you should do it. Just
like, you know, edit your claw.md or
make a little doc in your repo or
something. People are obsessed by this
idea that agents should just remember
things over time, but actually I find it
just works better if you kill the memory
completely.